Ernst back next part Ah a
just gonna read
on backwards I and I measured and then Let's
see the new new and aluminum a like
this top DJ of bananas and appreciations who
China Saturday in God
when you said that when you drink from talks
about
these of cow bowl that are very
strong are very nice were
very nice in previous lives
very generous they didn't study but they didn't
understand me they emptiness inta
because they were so generous
or born as being very strong
and wealth badanta
Dan
attracts about and then talks
that if these came from themselves
then they shouldn't change and
that's the very difficult idea
week
that we should talk
about Christmas S8 And the question is after we
die on the weekend I mention or when we
came into this world you're going to
even put on clothes Why don't we remember
where we came from what do you do And it's a
big question
And
if we could remember
where we were before that we could
n't easily remember
previous lives
Then I think we would all be very
psychotronic  others and there would be no
international tension between populations What
peoples today and I think sometimes when
we study Buddhism video Nasol
Nasol we ask the obvious questions of
What are Why don't I remember
past lives If I had a
past life Why don't we remember
So it's absolutely complete and I take I
don't know this subject and if we're
honest with ourselves
many of us can say
a Masha a feeling of what it was a
Suceava Emotion sitting in my
past life but if you're from heaven you'll
say you don't really know and How many
remember clearly look you were
before sometimes the Boss you have an
earth sign and
psychologists a I think I wasn't a
good cook in past lives because I did
n't have a from the kitchen
Why Why don't I remember
past lives What is the reason and all this
whole story here in this
poem is
if you expect that you should remember
then you then you don't Understand Where are you
coming from if you think that  you should
remember is the previous ones means you don't
understand Where do you come from even you
still have a feeling that there is a euro
who had the previous life and who who
lived my life between the summer always
eco there is the middle way school
that says
yes I think Michael
psbtst a my consciousness And the fact that
I am the world while my thoughts
conscious of my thoughts that is
Michael and that seems to be correct I was
wrong black I now listen I
have a body
but I am not my finger The mistake is not his
finger counters to go out to has
fingers the mistake of have so
why is there a gesture and that
and has these fingers but is not the
fingers to
go out to the peavey bass So the mistake must
be somehow
a spirit a soul and Get scared you don't
feel And that spirit to move you between
life between other So it is the most that you
give him smile magic and he dies in this
life and we can see
psam let's see how the body goes somewhere else
and we have to bury him For
example I don't know live station
we feel that there must be a
real mistake that goes further that we go
further
and leaves this body and goes all over the
world
But I don't know what happens to the mind
the mind is invisible love you will
see the evidence of
another person's mind in the eyes
connects those people in his smile in
How he frowns you can see the evidence of the
mind's existence on his face
used you but I can't see Inter
other people
but feel that it's okay
if the mistake leaves his body it
means that he probably took it in his
mind with him after him but baby so at
this water match right up me and at
together with his mind the mistake
signals to be brought somewhere else for
another life and left this world and
then that will take another body later that's how we
talk And that's how we think
about this subject
of and at exists
in the choir How to
get and his body ages and gases to
come out of that car used
in free rein but and on we feel
this thing and that's what the first step talks about
none to me here
talks about like when  we change
lives we feel like it's like changing a
car an old car for a new car
and you move on
but what he's saying is here is that later there's no
one to get out of the
old car and there's no one to get into that
new car that You're not all that is
not Who are you really
and you also leave
this mind and the mind behind when you get out of the
old car instead of You leave your
body behind
and you leave behind your mind and the
identity of Michael it's not like there's a
Michael baird again at the
beam and I know Buddhism talks like that
here but it's a language problem It's
not true that Michael
gets out of his old body let's go
Bardot for 7 weeks 49 days and
then he gets into his new body It's not
true it's not right if it was like that
first and the old people then come on there must
be people who remember remember
past lives
Wait a minute the
kitchen clock is ringing for soup or something
pfai to us gaming name is to my mother
nicknamed me
Mr
missh I'm 30 years old she said that I'm the one who would of
all the pots in the monastery
and still would food
is not like you so Michael comes out of
his body goes somewhere else listen
to this will be talked about in this
Poem new seeds open up
a new counter appears Michael I'm not
a man
who changes cars from one life
to another it doesn't work like that
I have how my my seeds open
now freeze just as
special Phoenix and then
those seeds end
and the body the mistake stops and
his mind the mistake stops
Also
and then new seeds to open Ok
not after 10 minutes after I die there
is no exit to you at that
moment there
are only other seeds there are many
other seeds that open up and that
is a completely different person
Of course you don't remember what you
were before Naturally you don't remember
you are completely there
are completely other seeds to
open
Of course you can't remember you
Just no money it's just a new body
and it's a new mind
we realize it's not like he came out
of this old car
and went in between 9 in a new body it's not it doesn't
work that way it's
my seeds for the Car the
old car and for his mind counters
at
or finish
now to open new seeds
Let's do them and it'll be a
completely different person person
Of course you don't remember
anything because it's a different person and
different mind Ok and I know we don't
usually talk like that but
The objective of this poem here s d r e
g is very interesting
and I like to tell students
how much it's the lightning and the microphone
because the Michael invite to become a
puppy how much you her to become a
puppy a puppy Is it true
that the mistake to take Bardot and that
the spirit stays there for 7 weeks
be and then if he's lucky he
reincarnates no no it's not true
the seeds open
65 on  second 65 per secundum
So How long does it take under direct channel
character to get into a new car and to
get into roaming on 9 and to get into a
new person
and part of a one on 65 a second
So I don't know why we feel
safe
if more is
ok I have seven weeks to see what I'm going to do
people are going to take care of me come out to
pray for me it's
not that big The urgency I have seven
weeks in the bubble you are I
can choose my seeds for the
future
finish and your seeds will open
on 1 and on 65 per second it
takes less than a second to become
a dog you don't have to remember you don't have to
wait for Yes the
puppy's body to grow for you to take over
that body your whole mind and
your whole body can change between another
being
between a second in less than a
second don't
think you have 7 weeks to
prepare in part two to worry
and that I have seven weeks
to find a good body my next tube
of oxygen having their What seeds do you have
when you die those
are the ones that will decide What will
be the count life you don't even
choose it's
not your choice and your seeds
choose
then the seeds that you have in
your mind when you die you are are the ones that you will
believe yourself in the future
if you have good seeds
that person will be a very
ok happy person and every
negative you have will create a
negative guy the next life
So if there is any part of you
that comes from itself Then you can
say that the mistake goes bar 20 Let's
pray for him
maybe he can remember the
good seeds but it's not like that you left you
disappeared you lose your body
you are from the old car and the old mind
and then you become a new car with the new
mind it's not like me You are a driver
who changes cars It doesn't work so
here warfare checking These guys she
Let's get into the text belong
and there are we risk not finishing
this one is 100 years old he says Forget
those  super beings of you
By the way they are so powerful you have to
imagine
that it is a possibility for A
Afterlife
announced that kept margoss you know there
are those games where you play with
some
marble spheres in
[Music]
and they have the power to play with the planets it
hurts me gascanul But I don't understand why I do
n't understand that everything is a seed that
opens
Lidl How to connect with Touch and then
how how how how can I How
things start how things start
How things appear and we can
talk for a long time
about Why a good thing starts in
your life and why a bad thing starts
your life but in short you cannot make up
names you can't run a moment when
this pixa became pix can you say that
pix were made in Japan
when on November 3rd the
fans in 2020 came out of the factory Yes but
what is the exact moment when it became
on
discharge cool But mommy and I can't
find that moment you know I can't
find the exact moment  ready decrease in which
this pen became a pen
finish finish this text was not
at 9:00 and 30 minutes
and ten seconds since then it
left the factory And advice
nadăşa when yes yes but this is the moment when
you left the factory
left side or right side of the chest It does
n't matter the mistake with it matters that you
left the factory Bars But actually
it's a between a very difficult idea there
has to be one side of the
pen has to leave the factory first
if part You left the factory and
then the other side the other side
left the factory there has to be a
difference between the two sides that leave the
factory
and at a certain point the
right side of the pen came out and after a few
[Music]
seconds the other side came out Ok but the
middle when you left the
factory come out at but it really makes sense to
really matter on
dispose more when half when you
left if the factory increases to Who
cares listen I ca
n't tell you the exact moment when
the pen You  out of the factory
because they are pieces of time
Which are so short that you can't
see them try to understand A second a second
has a beginning and an end so much so much
has a beginning of time and
has an end of time and lasts a
period begins and ends
been clever you must also exist the
possibility that this period can be
cut in two
you choose your pack
exemplary I am getting ready to make a
cake for my wife today and they say it
is not healthy but I don't care
but when you are sick and someone makes you a
cake it makes you happy
and this this cake sister will
have several parts there will be a part from the
Top a part from the bottom and a part from the middle
and now we are listening to another part of the park if the
parts of the parts are too small to
see them
if you can't see Atomic
then you can't see any part
after dual his of his cake if you
can't see the pieces of the cake then you ca
n't see the cake at all the
mistake I know I can't see atoms
and experiences But when you put a lot of
atoms  together Boss you see them together no I don't
understand
when you put a lot of atoms together
and say look now I see the cake It's not
enough it's not too small but there has to
be an atom here And there has to
be an atom on the other side and you
see the edges of the atoms atoms
if you can't see the atoms you can't
see the
cake the cake the cake is not
made of atoms the cake comes from
you Time doesn't come to You time comes from
you Rebirth is always another
body for another mind it doesn't come to
you and it comes by itself it can't
come to you the
atoms in this text can't come in
to admin because you can't see it
they're too small you can't see yourself if
something is too small to be seen and
put together you couldn't see the
edge Anyway because because the
edges made of an atom of wax be the
edge of an atom if I can't if you can
see
phew I can't see the edge of
this pen added some that comes from you
if you're afraid that you've had a pretty
good life And you've done pretty good things
and after  you die you
end up having a pretty good car
That's the wrong idea that there is no
car
and it's not in drivers it's just an
exam are There are things that come out of
your seeds there's no one to
look and they come out of your seeds you
are you are from your seeds Ok you don't
look
what comes out of
seeds you are What comes out of seeds Ok the one who looks is to from
seeds don't think you're just that you
have a body a car and a job of
yours and Everything comes All comes from
seeds from your seeds
I think it's It's very interesting to me and
all the things in your life all the
colors All the sounds
all the shapes come from your seeds
psatta who sees them
well Also from your seeds and there's no one
else
from the access stairs Ok let's go to the
engine versus
very nice to me You have Rome's onion
waist Baciu my channel and generally
finer to stay on top etcetera I
really want to drink and I'm that's why
good Iorga we see justice my magic
part of the complexion Denisa
storyshift A story
that these vases
have very children  beautiful
and now Come on beautiful it's good to have is
called la e bombo
psychopedagogy my name is a friend of
mine so Veronica gave birth last week
I had some friends who had I gave
birth to
twins
and the mother was very happy and you
send me a picture of both children who were
breastfed at the same time and I wash my
hands Happy and she was very happy Come on ciao when you have a child
look it looks like
This child came out of your womb
and you feel proud proud
and you feel fulfilled take care
livejournal o I gave birth tools
being
original and I Charlie Charlie and I feel a
strong attraction to that being
but in fact he says here
that you don't see your children correctly you don't
understand Where do they come from here Child really
come from your seeds I what the hell II you
have those children or born from your seeds
you could create yourself
You created
pregnancy and you created the children that
came out of you and everything comes from
your seeds efficient destiny with exactly
if you understand Where do children
really come from aluminum and glass then like
when  you see them you will want to be
nice to everyone if you understand
Georgel Nut and Ness really created
the children that they namely seeds
vegetables from your mind
under the taxi Halep died and one of
Sometimes in the family I don't know why some
people
and I dear after I do Children
become much more compassionate I have often been
people who are
selfish
become much more compassionate after I
do Children and learn how to
sacrifice
to sacrifice their happiness for
someone else when I was in the diamond business hey hey hey come on
girl I had to
hire hundreds of people
to give them
job interviews a
z to come in we pfai 19 years old hundreds and
hundreds of people
and after a few years I realized
that mothers are extraordinary she they are
extraordinary employees if you want a
good employee Choose a mother because they know
how to sacrifice and stay up late
and finish their job
the father will go to bed then a
child cries to you said air So it's
always I hire my mother
Because they know how to sacrifice for
others  are So sometimes like this
when you see
a person who has a child examples a
long time you will realize that you are a
better person compassion and than
other times
from my observations and I am not a father
when you have a child
today mental illnesses increase because you become
angrier Love love you
become more selfish take care of
your child first and don't take care of
other people's children and discriminate first what they have
and after that this other hour I don't
have to take care of my neighbors take
care of my child
what is he talking about Here is that
this understanding
Teo namely Where do your children come from and he
talks about the children of the gods and he says you know I
wet Bobi in this tradition they
say that they
give you that that babies just
appear in his lap for a day they just
appear in the palms No pain without
anything to put
in is a it seems that it is a very
easy way to do with penny So the idea is from
here is now
a and we have that faster when
you give birth to a child are two
things happen 1 you will understand if I write so that we know that
this  this wonderful person
comes from your seeds
where you were generous to others and after a
little these the child you have to take even
more care of today the
ideal Psalm if you do not Understand Where the
child really comes from
then the birth of the child can be a
tragedy of living
possessive start and you no longer care about
others be
if you understand I what you have SpongeBob sift
food your child was born from seeds
then You will understand
that you should take
care of
other people's children equally A ok now
there is an interesting dynamic
with the gods drink clothes live their whole life
is is full of competition
Mr Juve very similar to a
with people rich people
in this world and I was listening to the radio
when I was coming back from work I have
when he wanted 45 minutes to get
home I have
because I live on a mountain
and there is also a
when when I get home at night it
is a very cautious road
and sometimes listen to the radio
and hear news about other places
other about other countries other states in
America
I mean desert package 60 Ok in different places
in you have
and come you get step and  I hear these famous
actors famous I
catch them and even to talk about who
I talk about other actors in other
movies
and they are very competitive in the
fireworks market and that's how these
very beautiful people
who look very good think
[Music]
very nice old man I don't
know why they don't have a belly of co I see that
wonderful
always Looks very good very
mobile deciduous I say but the
better you look physically
and than and the more I come be me so then the
habit is to become jealous
and to enter into competition with other
people
like a curse is a big
problem I
had their successful
their beautiful and rich people
sometimes feel like fish and to feel are
intense competition with each other
or envy each other
and now this is talked about and that
tells me you know about these people
who have a beautiful life
ready One shin guards tide hurler but I
take it one thing that defines their life the
most important and most important part
of their life is  envy seven It's not
enough to be number 1 It's not
enough to win I don't know what
Oscar but you
constantly check How are the others
If they are more beautiful or smarter
or more famous or stronger  c
private company washes Hamrun or that the
number of followers on social media
So exactly
I do but
this talks about
the emotions
of these gods
who are two great Moses a hoverboard
what when you have a child
I feel this intense love for
his child for their child
and then
when I see another of you another god
I feel this intense jealousy
and spirit of competitiveness
dysfunction to me says Be careful
gypsy
Let's think about these of e to
think about these very
beautiful rich people
texts Fain from Huawei P9 things
define life
one man shogun have children
are very attached to their children
and have a very beautiful love for
their children
but at the same time
I feel intense jealousy intense envy
towards other people have famous
powerful it's strange that these successful beings
have
these emotions of attachment and love
and competitiveness so intense a
pfai to weaker day and pension to me doesn't
say
A you should be a person Hello I
'm at bodypower you should
love others the way you
love your children not that Say
no that Say it's very interesting What it
says Do
n't forget the decision to be feet this time it's
a fight between the devil and the angel a
This is a fight between dm devil And
angels the devil says wrong Michael
in your mind There are
two different thoughts number one
you have great compassion for everyone
how beautiful
and number two you have intense jealousy towards
other teachers
no that Say no that Say equal first
I function at minus this say don't say
Be careful you have
good thoughts And you have bad thoughts
Come on please I nicely have more
good thoughts and try to less on
bad thoughts no that says he says
that nobody has those thoughts he says
that nobody has those thoughts
nobody has that love for the child
nobody feels about this is jealousy
for competitions for competition there
is nobody there
list
if the teacher still of marzipan day
Nexo Try to improve yourself multiply your
thoughts of love and
try to decrease your thoughts of
competition if someone Says that
means they have no idea what they are talking about
Because when they tell you that you
should do these  two agricultural works
psndl say this
I'm talking about you but it's not but you don't
exist that way
at the fight If you think there's someone
who has that compassion and if you think there's someone
who has
those feelings of calm
competitiveness it means you've already
lost the War and I'll repeat once you've had
time to see if you think there's a
you who has a loving thought and if
you think there's a you
who has a competitive thought and
if you think you should have more
loving thoughts and you think you should
have less
competitive thoughts you've already lost the War The
War has already taken out the devil because there's
no you there's no there's no one
who has those thoughts desert at the
finger of class if there's no
me who soul to improve and
if there's no me
who gets worse if I don't study
Then why do you say that pfai conversation
if there's no me there's no you there's
only seeds there's no
you nobody got out of
your old car and or got into the new car
wings
posts by  sending you a there is no
you there are only seeds that
open
seeds that open mistake if there is no me
then how can I be
happy who becomes a Buddha then he does
not become a Buddha
seeds of the lip open when you are Well yes
so don't worry about I
think I Hear
me Is someone who is with the microphone
open there is no
me see who has
beautiful thoughts There is no you are the
beautiful thoughts
you are your seeds that open
So don't worry about me about
me just worry about the seeds
when you see yourself loving towards
your children all you do is
look at your good seeds that
open when you see someone being
competitive towards other people all you do is
see seeds of
competition that open That's all
although I have to do now the mistake
try to understand
you look at the seeds How to open and you
have to focus on the seeds don't
focus on me on me don't
focus on yourself boconcept focus on the
seeds Cassian to me  hard to
meditate Yes I know how to open the seeds
look at the seeds with opening the last
thing and then we have questions Ok Tim you
still have soy end I said to tell a story a
few times but but dad But dad
He tells a lot and too
many Look this is my kitchen we
see
So it wasn't like me when you
trick me than to try and lately
when I wake up at night and go
into the kitchen to eat something he
keeps stepping on something drunk calm something wet you
water on the floor
and every night secretly
Tycoon I go into the kitchen and the
water is very cold
aya.ro 14 that here too it's winter in
Arizona and I think I feel responsible I
feel like I'm a bad person but I
have to He should clean the water on the
floor I think it's the second time like this and
clean the water on Yes
when someone else's Kinder on Oana Huawei and I do the
cleaning I did the cleaning Some
4 5 nights 6 nights
2010 by which evening I do this thing and
of all I don't know what to  happened
I said mommy tired of always cleaning the paste
Come on so much
of all variant I
have to drive as well as fix it
is much more work to always clean
water
So maybe I better look at the cause So this is what we
try here this is what we learn
here of dream have
a questionnaire Theory and iPad paint to
make you go over your head don't focus on the
result he thought equal I have a friend
my friend Daniel Garcia you have
repaired the
pipe
and says put I have it here
is take care of your seeds don't
focus on the result focus on the
seeds you will take care of your seeds
also
when you feel an intense love for
your children special what and felt
strong envy at work
those two also come from seeds
why do you take care of those seeds don't
worry about yourself stop
thinking about wrong more Cute more that the
calmest Escape put Come on Love comes
from seeds and envy holds from seeds
and I'm wrong Michael
who is envious came from seeds and
care Michael loving also comes from
seeds So work on your seeds fix them
Fix them  mistakes fix the
pipe that flows the
problem is that the person who works
on seeds
comes from Oz also from seeds
the person who works on seeds
pfai us also from seeds So
what seeds do you have more but are you sure
that possible do the more
good seeds you have the more you are A better worker a
better gardener or not And there is no
one who is in control now With what
seeds do you have about What seeds now are
similar to tomorrow's seeds because they
are created by the person who works on
seeds
we don't care too much about the questionnaires if
y3 that there is a problem with the seeds I have a little
and a problem and with the person who repairs the
seeds
of and to call this tonight they don't have the one
Gracias
what you say call a the fact that we can't
improve It is difficult but
it is impossible as long as you understand
that things come from seeds Then you can
here hope and if you forget that then you
have no hope Focus Sat
still on seeds focus on
still on seeds ep
if you have bad seeds it is because you
come from bad seeds you are too from
bad seeds the mistake and when I
can fix myself
How can I fix my nose seeds
bad if I come from seeds bad
today Sounds like it's impossible not
because you can do small things
We are very lucky
that seeds grow We are very lucky
that seeds grow doubles doubles
from Plaza doubles you can do
one thing more that today if you can do
one small thing a day
are and there is hope because those
seeds doubles dances
doubles Ok so today
a practical step if you want to have a
good rebirth
when time a nice little thing so be
a nice place good thing nice I make a
soup today is not the best in the
world I
am not in very good cook is both
on My country is better than to
But do small things nice for others
and dedicated Dedicate those seeds to others
legendary and me and let's dedicate we
all dedicate the seeds for the seeds
to find a solution to resolve the
tension these internet Alex of the
conflict International subarov let me
tell you tomorrow now came out this soup If I
die or not
it's a good little thing dichel Dedicate
seeds the seeds  and the seeds will
explode
was mind plant small good seeds
and to let them grow
victim what questions do you have for me
Hriscu street is
here so Nichifor fitness the other
thank you for teaching us today
thank you for the questions
of bringing into the
picture
advocacy this this
question refers to
pfai central to get over your mind don't
focus on the result when we talk about
seeds in several schools For example
how is the school more in two days no more
Mind that the seeds are stored in the
refrigerator
or are there more schools in which to say that the
seeds are stored in me
itself can you explain to us what more
about Why are we
talking and how are we talking about how the
seeds Are stored in us Find
and ham ham to focus over the mind
when the seeds are not outside us
Loghin to go with it Be careful in the
lower schools
we can say and a good person
try to plant good seeds PSI
then when you die you will
get a better body better score
and it will be a better place
sense of I know I this time is the first
first  spin show
pass negativism equal as it is please apnea
plant good seeds you will die you will die
and for that you need good seeds
and you can think that you hold them like
a suitcase and you can open them
What Pension says to me here is John shaw
gas is that don't forget that the person
who works with the seeds
is created by the seeds at the same time
Ok
So the person who tries to
improve
pubs the person
who makes the seeds who plants the
seeds of a new at that time
also comes from the seeds I'll convince you
end they
want standards So if you understand that
this thing you have a chance happened and they
open but if you think there is
someone who makes the seeds who doesn't come
from the seeds at the same time then come then you
have a problem you have a problem That's it So
try to understand
that the one who makes the seeds
comes from from the seeds For example
intensified mecheres if
if the one who plants the seeds is
in good condition today then he will plant
good seeds and if if about milk the
seeds are in bad condition
then try to plant to make the seeds
will make bad seeds  So you
have to understand
that the one who makes the seeds that creates the
seeds also comes from the seeds
and we have to
plant the seeds that will make us a
level transform into a better gardener the
gardener also comes from the seeds
So we have to be careful
lantic their rights is at Atlanta
good seeds to be a good gardener
So we have to spend some time
thinking
ymf Why am I
happy when you plant seeds
why why do I believe in seeds why am I happy
for seeds there are special seeds to
believe in seeds
and that is the root of all seeds
they say put the one I have here the first
financial plan at ma is to take care of that
gardener who makes the seeds why did you
come to this class today because
you have Planted the seeds in the past take care
of those seeds Ok don't lose those
seeds which means it's cold
encourage others every time you
see someone
doing something good say he drank How cool is this what is this
doing here this thing
with enjoying for Alex
and the coffee meditation psychiatrist all
those at this is true  seed
to become a good gardener Take
care of your gardener of
your gardener seeds and what is the
best way
is to tell others How nice
you are cool I am and do this all the time and
by the way don't lie don't
make up stories to be an ox and
tell him that he is great eyes this file
third Hello not at all I
say this what I am saying is that when
you see something really good and that
someone else is doing
say of How cool is it
and it is Somehow selfish
if you don't tell others How cool am I and
How cool is what Stefan Here I saw
when you talked to that person
maybe difficult you are so cool Come on so
much patience I
just want to say that is very cool What you did
and I really liked to
be patient or patient like you
So these seeds of encouragement towards
other people make you a
better gardener is very cool a touch of pa
pa So you look at others You notice
others and you encourage them to do I
encourage them with a  I feel reality to
continue doing what I do That
makes you a better gardener See
this is what Pension la ma talks about where we plant the
seeds school
may in the field is useful
word just finished the first book
origin
shishito just finished the first book
about school no longer lies and I think it
is the
best book about school no longer lies
in history I think it is the best
book I have ever seen
about school may in two RON
and is published by the publishing house
elpress
Ready it is called the Golden Key
And if you want to really understand
school no longer lies
then that book and
chew it and ask what I saw that they
will hold
so please bear to teach The
book is absolutely Wonderful Amazing
I read a sentence recently Which
simply
wow it's about the account wooden hoe
see Ok bye
and said Be careful
if you really understand
school may in two months only lies
the idea no longer lies about about the place
where your seeds
only then can you practice tantra
for him and only then Which That
I think is full of success
you can live with angels if I really
understand this is with the refrigerator where the
seeds are stored and I was Wow
this It's super cool the
right terms gessler and a lot of
people said the mistake a I bought tibco
a can enjoy the nest immediately
or I'll order online and
receive enjoy next second That's too you do
n't have to wait for the mail
interesting if not America if I wait The
mail at the end of the year for days until
you receive a book
so you can receive enjoy in a few
minutes I think it's
worth it is perfect and many people have
said a mistake at school no longer lies
is much too difficult but they are one
thing you can do number 1
is on the blog has not difficult if a book
is not difficult it means you already
understand it And then there is no reason
to buy the book
if a book is is easy then it is
because you understand what is written there
so in my opinion I should not
buy the book before reason to buy  the
book if you already understand something
PSI should buy the book has no
spasm in my opinion in and in
his tradition to fit we should
buy the books we don't understand
wishes to get I hope we should
because only then can we go
into depth
and the crazy nuts this team mix node
are extraordinary and work very
hard each of them understand their
book very well and I want to show you
something
[Music]
even Suites hotel jigo
What does the Iasi train station mean they have arranged
weekend
may I show you I have this in the
mixtape classes you can see my screen
Psalm I really are not to draw
a head of and you can read could we
come the crazy salons and read
this thing These are the topics in
ecstasy and I give you I give you in preview to
believe don't say tonic
and I hope exception pizza Look where it
came from These are the original settings
from 2,500 years ago it's not we translate six
of them of
love and then  we have
abidal me the higher knowledge
about 2,000 years ago how to
go after which appear are the
mahayana books from 1,800 years ago I see
and then comes the school I don't lie anymore as pas
anga
750 years ago
you argued me and then comes but ma but
machiate tri and the school took reason
and clear thinking or tantric now what to
years 1,500 years
and then comes that great morality
and in the case of hand dynastar and then appears the
Tang dynasty in China
with its team team of body of
translators
and then appears the Lower Middle Way
and namely that took me and to in
and writers like lamb
who loved meditation
and books about meditation appeared the
great books about meditation
how But what Mihai Eminescu after which
appeared the Upper Middle Way this
Even if Even if Katy and those who
truly understand
emptiness some excellent guys This is
1,500 years ago
and then I get how to develop a
good heart And that was a thousand years ago
years
and then it appeared at brem
and about 600 years ago when
he lived or in k state other defects
removed and then the study of
different schools appeared in two ways
namely
studying all schools together
These are all the great ideas again the
last 2,500 years
a in and now cabbage
I'll make this smaller
ok and it's a speaker Ok but oh and these are
the books this in the books that we
produce
we translate 600 re
pills that cover the greatest
topics of the last 2,000 years
dear you we don't have the Chance king and we have 27
translation And if you don't take them it means
you're crazy
you're crazy if you don't buy
these books So if you have time next week
we'll have 60 class
about this idea that you asked
now I asked again it's
our son distant if you really want to
understand how seeds sit in your mind
Come to mixmods from that crazy peanut
because we translate very very long
time let's have another Question  let's
see accommodation Costinești
above I know this is a question this is a
complex question
someone asked
about his partner
is his partner who seems to no
longer love his Family
is something else asks about the fact that he
seems to no longer have compassion for
others of and could you advise us
for these two situations
as almost similar in which we no longer
feel so many positive emotions
without street examples is one of the
saddest things in the world on the one
hand are
you a relationship
it seems that the other person is no longer
interested or it seems that I no longer
love you and I loved you as much
Nane pfai this is It is is like you
feel that it will rush through your fingers
this person if you're Happy ending
is you can feel How does Edge happen to be
nice it can stay the person
is skin is my partner my partner has been
with me for a long time but I no longer
have the passion I no longer feel passion for
this person
cauliflower but I feel like it
helped him or something
and Both are very unpleasant feelings
you owe love to my family but I don't
feel
or
For example someone in the family  my or
child from the campaign I work in doesn't
seem to seem to not have much
passion for me
for How they used to and These are
afraid that they are the same to do similar
these feel the same it feels like you do
n't have love anymore is
lost Love I know you can do
this you halogen
psychic once we are lucky
because the first law of flesh is says that
all seeds grow fast
So the first law of karma says
that seeds double every 24
hours If you understand seeds Ok So
that's super Call
is like a super fertilizer
if you understand flax seeds neck
sure then the good seeds that I
plant will grow like us  good
crazy or excess
But if you see that love is lost
it's like water on the floor Don't
try to clean it up the water on the floor namely
namely Repair repair the pipe to that
drips
his personally
and I've lived a long life I've seen a lot of
things it's not all with him yours doesn't
work I think
cigarettes of the psychic processes to go to
a person and say ba It seems to me
that there's not much Love love in
your heart You can improve a little
that I family a partner who loves you
try to it me and you mother you
my love I can't say it doesn't work like that because
why does it come from you how
much love does this person have
comes from you
So you don't you have anything to do but
plant more seeds of love and
that can be appreciation So
think of the people I come feeding a I serve you
who helps you is someone who
grows oranges from which the
oranges come for this trick Is
there someone who planted the
coffee seeds for my coffee that I
drink now yes Is
there someone who  planted
watermelon for My hive is so
many people who care about me I should show my
appreciation and
love for these people Even
just gratitude for these people
in the winter in Arizona it's very
very cold I'm in the Mountains but someone
Says someone sends me electricity
Thank you I don't know who it's because of but
I know that if I pay my bills I've been
good the mountain top brings Come on
just try to
show gratitude for all the
good things in your life
and that's it I plant the seed
So that love doesn't disappear and comes
back into your life I have love the
love of a partner or a family member
your love for your family the
love other than yourself
Can I replant it as you can laugh
trigger that spark of love
showing gratitude to those who
do things for you the
equipment to thank you
for the internet many time
for organizing these classes and for
working all day and all
night to give us so many
chances to learn more and love will
come back and It's really fun
for kids the censure motion and it comes
from seeds it
's really really nice
to know how to bring your love back
into your heart they're from others to you it
's so cool
to be able to
improve let the Light
love in your heart right from
your point of view it's like you're
fixing the leaky pipe ok ok